Guide to the Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project Records 1976-1986
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project Records
1976-1986
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 206
Washington State University. International Programs Support Office. Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project.
26 Linear feet of shelf space 26 boxes
The Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project, 1979-1986, aimed to meet the needs of the Western Sudan by: providing training; improving the agricultural research capabilities of four Western provinces; and raising the standard of living for subsistence farmers and pastoralists. The records of the Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project include travel records, travel reports, field notes, quarterly reports, financial records, and correspondence, both from on-campus and in-country.
The Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project, 1979-1986, was funded by the United States Agency for International Development and the World Bank. The Agricultural Research Corporation, research division of the Government of Sudan's Ministry of Agriculture, was a partner in the research program. The Consortium for International Development, of which Washington State University is a member, signed with the University's International Programs Development Office in August 1979 to implement the work. Washington State University provided the leadership and administrative support. The World Bank, initiator of the original plan, remained a co-funder, paying for the purchase and operation of an airplane to transport goods and personnel across the 350,000 square miles of the project.
The project aimed to meet the needs of the Western Sudan by: providing training; improving the agricultural research capabilities of four Western provinces; and raising the standard of living for subsistence farmers and pastoralists. Located in Kadugli, a city in Southern Kordofan, the project sought to improve the quality of life for the peoples of this area and the rest of the Sudan.
A list of abbreviations associated with the Sudan project is included below.
The records of the Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project are arranged in two series: On-Campus Correspondence Files and In-Country Correspondence Files. These two series contain travel records, travel reports, field notes, quarterly reports, financial records, and correspondence.
The On-Campus Correspondence Files are filed alphabetically by subject or, when appropriate, numerically. In-Country Correspondence Files are also filed alphabetically by subject.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Records of the International Programs Support Office's Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project were transferred to the Washington State University Libraries in 1988 (accession number UA88-11).
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. International Programs Support Office. Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project -- Records and correspondence.; Agricultural Research Corporation of Sudan -- Records and correspondence.; Agricultural Research Corporation of Sudan.; World Bank. Eastern Africa Regional Office. Country Programs Department I.
Agriculture -- Research -- Sudan -- Archival resources.
Agriculture; Colleges and Universities; Washington (State)
- Series 1: On-Campus Correspondence Files
  - Aircraft
    - Bids, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Insurance, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Personnel, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Technical Description Manuals, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Budget
    - AID Budget Summaries, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - AID to CID Vouchers, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - AID Expenditures, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Audit, AID, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Audit, CID, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
    - Audit, U.S. Auditor General, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Budget Development, Cost Estimates, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Budget Development, General, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Budget Development, Khartoum Headquarters, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Budget Development, Sudan, World Bank, Quarterly Budget, Summary, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Budget Development, Trainee Research Costs, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Budget Development, Work Copies, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Budget Materials, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19-22)
    - Budget Preparation, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Budget Close-out Items, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Budget Summaries, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
    - Budget Summaries, Close-out Items, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Budget Summaries, Coding, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - CID Budget, Projections and Summaries, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - CID Dollar Trust Account, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 30-34)
    - CID Temporary Trust Fund Account, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 35-37)
    - CID/WSARP Trust Account, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38-41)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Current Budget Figures, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Field Support, Henry Bergman, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Finance Regulations, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Financial Report, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - General, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Karplen Supervision Receipts, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Summaries of Educational Allowances, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Precontract Projection and Summaries, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 50-55)
    - Projection and Summaries, WSU Office, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - WSU Accounts, Revolving, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 57-70)
    - WSU Accounts, Revolving, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 71-101)
    - WSU Coded Monthly Summaries (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - WSU Correspondence, Revolving Account, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - WSU Correspondence Pending Final Reconciliation, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - WSU Reconciliation of Cash Advance, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - WSARP Technical Assistance Budget, Working Papers, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Working Papers, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Working Papers, WSU Office, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Committees
    - Advisory Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 109-110)
    - Coordinating Committee, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Discussion, Khartoum, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Farming Systems Workshop, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Other Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Planning Meeting, In-Country, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - WSARP, Staff Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - WSARP Research Planning Meeting, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 117-118)
  - Conferences, Oafalla, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Construction-Contract
    - Architect, 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Contract Instruction for Tendering Contract, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Contracting and Trading Co., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Construction Supervision Report, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - General Work, Plans/Tender Analysis, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 124-125)
    - Grube Zimmer, 1979-1987 (Box 4, Folder 126-130)
    - Karplan Associates, Subcontract, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Karplan Associates Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Construction-Implementation
    - Advertisement, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 133-134)
    - Construction, Firm Selection, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Construction, Grube Zimmer, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Construction, Implementation--Library Plans, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Construction--Value Engineering Report, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Consultants, General, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Consultants
    - Clarence Becker, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - D. Dwyer, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Hamaeda El Sammani, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - A.E. Hall, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - J. Holechek, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - V. Jarret, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - L. King, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - A. Krezdorn, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Robert LaRacque, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - James Maguire, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Lynn McDonald, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Donald Minehart, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Earl Muir, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Ernest Nunn, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Phillip Oviatt, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - James J. Riley, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - LeRoy Rogers, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Raghuram S.V. Shetty, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Tom Trail, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Trevor Wilson, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Correspondence--AID, 1977-1986 (Box 5, Folder 160-188)
  - Correspondence--CID
    - Administrative, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 189-191)
    - Audits, 1984-185 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Budget, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Construction, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - Contracts, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - General, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - Project Reports, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - Staff, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Correspondence--Field Staff
    - Administrative Assistant, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 199-204)
    - Agricultural Economist, Patrick, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - Agronomist, Gingrich, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Agronomist, Woldatatios, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - Anthropologist, Araujo, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - Anthropologist, Michaels, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - Anthropologist, Teitelbaum, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - Chief Administrative Officer, Hannum, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - Chief Administrative Officer, Shurtteff, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Chief Administrative Officer, Stenquist, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 213-214)
    - Chief of Party, Hawood, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 215-216)
    - Chief of Party, Hogan, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 217-218)
    - Chief of Party, Owens, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 219-222)
    - Chief of Party, WSARP Field Staff, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 223-229)
    - Field Staff, Engineer, Higgins, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Field Staff, Livestock Production, Cook, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 231-232)
    - Field Staff, Maintenance Administration, Mannion, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Field Staff, Range Management, Bunderson, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - Field Staff, Soil and Water Specialist, Arya, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 235-236)
    - Financial Officer, WSU, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 237-238)
    - In-country, News Report, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - In-country, Staff Meeting, 1980-1985 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Sudan Staff, Abu Sabah, 1979-1986 (Box 7, Folder 241-242)
    - Sudan Staff, ARC, Director General, 1979-1985 (Box 7, Folder 243-246)
    - Sudan Staff, El Hussein, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Sudan Staff, General, 181-1985 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Sudan Staff, Mukhtar, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Sudan Staff, Osman, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Sudan Staff, Project Director, Dafalla, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 250-253)
    - Telexes, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 254-260)
    - Telex Numbers, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - WSARP, Work Copies, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - World Bank, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Insurance
    - Med/Vac, Bunderson, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - Miscellaneous Implementation, Vehicle, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 265)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - WSARP, General, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Inventory
    - Equipment Inventory System, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - Inventory, Printout from Disks, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 269)
    - Work Plans, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Library Plans, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Mail, APO Mailing Records, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Occasional Papers
    - Abo Elgasim, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 273)
    - Aryo, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 274)
    - Berhe, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 275)
    - Bunderson, et al., 1982-1986 (Box 9, Folder 276-288)
    - Cook, et al., 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 289-302)
    - Dafalla, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 303-304)
    - Dregne, Trip Report, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - D'Silva, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - Dwyer, Trip Report, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    - Mohamed Eisa, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 308)
    - El Sammani and Ahmed, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 309)
    - Fadlalla, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 310)
    - Fadlalla and Cook, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 31l)
    - Ghobrial, Trip Report, 1981, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 312)
    - Gillard-Byers Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 313-315)
    - Gillard-Byers, et al., 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 316-324)
    - Gingrich, Trip Report, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - Gotsch, Wright, Final Report, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Hall, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - Hannum, Final Report, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Harwood, Trip Report, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - Hastay, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Henson, Trip Report, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Higgins, Reports, 1980-1986 (Box 9, Folder 332-333)
    - Hogan, Final Report, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - Holechek, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Kenane and El Madina, Dow, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - LaRocque, Final Report, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Mannion, Final Report, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - McDonald, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Michael, et al., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 340-342)
    - Minehart, Final Report, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Noel, et al., 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 344-346)
    - Nunn, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 347-348)
    - Omer, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - Owens, Final Report, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Oviatt, Trip Report, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - Patrick, Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 352-357)
    - Riley, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 358-363)
    - Rogers, Final and Trip Reports, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 364-366)
    - Mark Speece, Gillard-Byers, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - Stenquist, End of Tour Report, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Suluman, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Teitelbaum, Final and Trip Reports, 1983- 1984 (Box 10, Folder 369-372)
    - Trail, Trip Report, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - Wilson, Trip Report, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Woldetatois, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 375-377)
    - Yousef, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Participant Training
    - Abdel Ageeb, 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 379-381)
    - ARC Trainees, 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - Sid Beteik, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - D. A. Dafalla, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - El Amin, 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 385-386)
    - El Awed, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - El Dukher, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - El Feel, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - El Hadi, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 390-391)
    - El Madi, Mohammed Ali (Box 10, Folder 391.1)
    - El Madina, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 392-393)
    - El Rahman, Muhammed Muttasim (Box 10, Folder 393.1)
    - El Wakeel, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 394-395)
    - Eldor, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - Eltam, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - General Information, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 398-399)
    - General Information, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 400-401)
    - Ibrahim, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 402)
    - Inactives, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 403)
    - Mobida, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 404-405)
    - Mekki, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 406-407)
    - Omer, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 408-409)
    - Project Information Form, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Rahma, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 411-412)
    - Seed, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 413-414)
    - Sidahmed, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Siddig, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 416)
    - Short-term, Abu El Gasim, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Short-term, Abu Sabah, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - Short-term, Al Eid, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 419)
    - Short-term, Ali, at al. 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Short-term, Fadlalla, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - Short-term, Hashim, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Short-term, Kanani, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Short-term, Khidir, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Short-term, Mukhter, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Short-term, Osman, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 426-427)
    - Sudan Training (Abu Sabah) (Box 11, Folder 426.1)
    - Trainees, English as a Second Language, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Trainees, General, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 429-430)
    - Trainees, Medical Forms, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 431-432)
    - Working File, Trainees (Box 11, Folder 432.1)
  - Personnel
    - "Arya - Lalit," 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 433-434)
    - Antonio Cenidozo, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - Joe R. Gingrich, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - John Hannum, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 437)
    - Robert E. Harwood, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 438)
    - David Higgins, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 439)
    - Shirley Higgins, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 440)
    - LeMoyne Hogan, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    - Michael Mannion, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    - Barbara Michael, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - Medical Evaluation Insurance, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 444)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Gerald Owens, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - Neil A. Patrick, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - James Riley, 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 448-449)
    - Miller F. Shurtleff, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 450)
    - Lee Stenquist, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 451)
    - Joel Teitelbaum, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 452)
  - Personnel--In-country Hire
    - Tareke Berhe, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 453)
    - Stephen Horton, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 454)
    - Montoya Shawga, et al., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 455)
    - Perlita Sulite, 1977-1983 (Box 12, Folder 456)
  - Personnel--Short-term
    - Rita Fisher, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 457)
    - Laird Hastay, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 458)
    - Richard Knott (Box 12, Folder 458.1)
    - Lynn McDonald, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 459)
    - Alice Spitzer, 1985, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 460)
    - William Symons, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 461)
    - Tom Trail, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 462)
  - Personnel--WSU Classified Staff
    - Kathryn Nicholas, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 463)
    - Barbara Sourcall, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 464)
    - Mary Smythe Vacher, 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 465)
  - Personnel-- Time-Slip
    - Steve Bailey, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 466)
    - Elizabeth Erdman, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 467)
    - Charla Harness, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 468)
    - Rachel Pate, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 469)
    - Stuart Paterson, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 470)
    - Scott Schwinge, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 471)
    - Time Slip, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 471.01)
    - Kathleen Walker, 1986-1986 (Box 12, Folder 472)
    - Laura Williams Mattler, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 473)
  - Project Control Register:
    - Accountant, Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 474)
    - Budget, Working, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 475-477)
  - Publication--Book Orders
    - Blackwell North American, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 478)
    - England and North America, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 479)
    - Babo Fadlalla, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 480)
  - Publication--Book Requests
    - General, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 481)
    - Ibrahim Hashim, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 482)
    - David Higgins, et al., 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 483)
    - Abdebrahman, et al., 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 484)
    - University of Bergen, Norway, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 485)
  - Publication--Ordered Books, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 486)
  - Publication--Purchase Orders, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 487-488)
  - Publications
    - Follow-ups, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 489)
    - Journal Subscriptions, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 490)
    - Literature Search, R. Cook, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 491)
    - Purchasing, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 492-493)
    - Purchasing, Purchase Orders, Arya, Lalit, and Bunderson, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 494)
    - WSARP Publications List, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 495)
  - Publicity
    - Photographs, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 496)
    - Reports (Copies), 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 497)
    - Talks, Jan Noel, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 498)
    - WSARPost, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 499)
  - Purchasing
    - Correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 13, Folder 500-501)
    - Arkel International, Inc., 1984-185 (Box 13, Folder 602)
    - Circle Air Freight, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 503)
    - Equipment and Furniture Lists, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 504)
    - Equipment Requests, In-process, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 505)
    - Library Equipment and Supplies, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 506)
  - Purchasing and Shipping
    - Logbooks, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 507-508)
    - Logbooks, Publications, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 509)
    - Procedures for WSARP, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 510)
    - Seed Orders, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 511)
    - Status Reports, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 512)
  - Related Projects/Organizations
    - Abyei Development Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 513-514)
    - AID Projects, Agricultural Planning/Statistics, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 515)
    - AID Trypanosomiasis Control Project, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 516)
    - Bibliography; Thomas Fuller, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 517)
    - Bibliography; Steven Ira Londner, "Agricultural Development in the Sudan's Gezira Scheme," 1982 (Box 13, Folder 518)
    - Blue Nile Project, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 519)
    - CIMMYT Farming Systems, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 520)
    - CIMMYT Farming Systems Proposals, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 521)
    - Cooperative Arid Land Research Program, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 522)
    - Hunting Technical Services, Bibliography and Notes, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 523)
    - International Agricultural Development Services, Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 624)
    - INTSORMIL Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 525)
    - INTSORMIL, Agricultural Research Corporation Report, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 526)
    - INTSORMIL, Annual and Progress Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 527)
    - INTSORMIL, Sudan Agricultural Research Corporation, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 528)
    - INTSORMIL, Systems Reports (Farming), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 529)
    - International Soybean Program, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 530)
    - Kansas State University, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 531)
    - Khartoum University, Veterinary Science, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 531.01)
    - KORAG PP, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 532)
    - Kordofan University, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 532.01)
    - Nitrogen Fixation Program (Iowa State), 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 533)
    - Nuba Mountain Project, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 534)
    - Rahad Irrigation Project, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 535)
    - Veterinary Research Administration, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 536)
    - Veterinary Research Administration, Animal Production Trainee Transcripts, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 537)
    - Western Savannah Development Corporation Review, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 538)
    - Western Project Concept Paper, "Extension," 1983 (Box 13, Folder 539)
    - Western Sudan Water Supply Project, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 540)
    - Yambio Research Station, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 541)
  - Related Projects/Reports--AID/CID
    - Commodity Import Program Grant, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 542)
    - CID Annual Reports, 1979-1984 (Box 13, Folder 543)
    - CID Mid-term Reports, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 544)
    - CID Team Report, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 545)
    - CID Team Report, Supplementary Report, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 546)
    - County Development Strategy Statement, BIFAD Review, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 547)
    - County Development Strategy Statement, USAID Project Papers, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 548)
    - Fiscal Year 1984, Sudan Funding, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 549)